reconsideration.org 2018-01-19

# Privacy Policy - reconsideration.org

This is the web site of RECONSIDERATION.ORG, a provider of SEO Services and SEO Software

Our postal address is:

381 Broadway, Box 8  
Menands, NY 12204

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@Reconsideration.org.com](mailto:info@Measurableseo.com) or you can reach us via the [contact page](http://measurableseo.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

This Privacy Policy describes the information RECONSIDERATION.ORG, may collect about you through your use of the RECONSIDERATION.ORG search engine optimization service and related web sites (collectively, the “RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site”). It also describes how RECONSIDERATION.ORG uses your information, how RECONSIDERATION.ORG protects it, and what choices you have on how that information is used.

**Information Collection and Use by RECONSIDERATION.ORG**

RECONSIDERATION.ORG collects and uses information voluntarily submitted by a user, such as a user’s name, email address, URLs, keywords, and credit card payment information, in connection with the services provided by RECONSIDERATION.ORG on behalf of such user. RECONSIDERATION.ORG may also share such information with its affiliated companies and business partners (such as agents or subcontractors) who are acting on RECONSIDERATION.ORG’s behalf to support your customer relationship with RECONSIDERATION.ORG, unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law.

RECONSIDERATION.ORG may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site. This data is used to manage the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to visitors. User IP addresses may also be recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

RECONSIDERATION.ORG may also use a user’s email address to send updates, such as a newsletter or news regarding RECONSIDERATION.ORG’s products and services. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by clicking an “opt out” link located at the bottom of the update.

Unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law, information collected by RECONSIDERATION.ORG may be (i) used by RECONSIDERATION.ORG for marketing and business purposes, (ii) retained by RECONSIDERATION.ORG indefinitely, and (iii) sold or otherwise transmitted to third parties.

**Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Systems**

RECONSIDERATION.ORG may use cookies or other similar tracking means to store user’s preferences and to record session information. RECONSIDERATION.ORG may link the information it stores in its tracking systems to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some tracking systems, or notify you when a tracking systems is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your tracking system preferences — however, you may have to enable tracking systems from RECONSIDERATION.ORG in order to use some functions on the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site.

**Links**

The RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site may contain links to other sites. RECONSIDERATION.ORG is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information RECONSIDERATION.ORG Collects**

In addition to the disclosures otherwise described in this privacy statement, RECONSIDERATION.ORG may disclose personal information to a third party if RECONSIDERATION.ORG believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by RECONSIDERATION.ORG, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of RECONSIDERATION.ORG’s products and services. RECONSIDERATION.ORG reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of RECONSIDERATION.ORG or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time RECONSIDERATION.ORG may make changes to its privacy policy. If RECONSIDERATION.ORG makes changes, it will post them on the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site so users will be aware of what information RECONSIDERATION.ORG collects, how RECONSIDERATION.ORG uses it, and when RECONSIDERATION.ORG may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, RECONSIDERATION.ORG is going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection it will notify you by posting a notice on the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site for 30 days.

**Contacting RECONSIDERATION.ORG**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site, or your dealings with the RECONSIDERATION.ORG Site, please contact us at: [info@Reconsideration.org.com](mailto:info@measurableseo.com).
